<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>shyuni &#8211; wordpress-1357380-4992777.cloudwaysapps.com</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/shyuni/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Brand Buzz: October&#039;s social media highlights</title>
		<link>/brand-buzz-octobers-social-media-highlights/</link>
					<comments>/brand-buzz-octobers-social-media-highlights/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brand-buzz-octobers-social-media-highlights/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Campaign rounds up what brands got up to on socials last month.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><img decoding="async" src="https://cached.imagescaler.hbpl.co.uk/resize/scaleHeight/815/cached.offlinehbpl.hbpl.co.uk/news/OMC/brandbuzz.jpg" style="width: 100%" /></p>
<div>Campaign rounds up what brands got up to on socials last month.</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/brand-buzz-octobers-social-media-highlights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Etsy Holiday Campaign Answers Waldo&#8217;s Existential Dilemma</title>
		<link>/etsy-holiday-campaign-answers-waldos-existential-dilemma/</link>
					<comments>/etsy-holiday-campaign-answers-waldos-existential-dilemma/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/etsy-holiday-campaign-answers-waldos-existential-dilemma/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[People love looking for Waldo – it’s his whole raison d’etre. But how much do they really know the striped, bespectacled character? Waldo is the star of Etsy‘s holiday campaign, which delves into the mind of the children’s book character that debuted in 1987. Agency Orchard Creative is behind the ads that aim to make [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>People love looking for Waldo – it’s his whole raison d’etre. But how much do they really know the striped, bespectacled character? </p>
<p>Waldo is the star of Etsy‘s holiday campaign, which delves into the mind of the children’s book character that debuted in 1987. Agency Orchard Creative is behind the ads that aim to make Etsy a top gifting destination for shoppers. </p>
<p>In the minute-long hero spot, Waldo moves through the world, musing that “they always ask, ‘Where’s Waldo?’ not ‘Who’s Waldo?’” While he admits he enjoys being in a crowd, Waldo feels unsatisfied by the fact that strangers constantly search for him but don’t get to know him. </p>
<p>Only when his girlfriend Wenda gives him a customized compass from Etsy does Waldo feel truly “seen.”</p>
<p>In a second ad, it’s Waldo who’s on the hunt, this time for the perfect holiday gifts. He uses Etsy to find presents for Wenda and his dog Woof, both of whom also sport his iconic red and white stripes. </p>
<p>“We wanted to create a campaign that captures the emotional magic of meaningful gift-giving – how Etsy sellers create gifts that make people feel truly seen and understood,” Etsy chief brand officer Brad Minor told ADWEEK. “Our holiday campaign highlights how Etsy sellers aren’t just making products, they’re creating moments of connection.”</p>
<p>To convey this message, Orchard decided to “use a beloved character in a totally new way,” said group creative director Heather Larimer. </p>
<p>“In showing how gifts can make people feel seen, we thought it would be interesting to use a flat character that everyone thinks they know, but then turn him into a real person that a great friend truly understands and values,” Larimer told ADWEEK. </p>
<p>Another holiday ad will debut on Nov. 11. “Hunter” is about a family’s dog and the role an Etsy gift plays in preserving the pet’s memory after his death.</p>
<p>The Waldo anthem will air in the U.S. and U.K. on Friday (Nov. 1), with “Hunter” launching on Nov. 11. An out-of-home campaign featuring life-size placements in New York, London, and Washington, D.C. will showcase original items from Etsy sellers as gifts for friends, a new mom, granddaughters, and a grandpa. Each uses the tagline,“Give ‘I get you’ gifts.” </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/etsy-holiday-campaign-answers-waldos-existential-dilemma/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Campaign Trail: Taco Bell takes on ‘Big Chicken’ through family debates</title>
		<link>/campaign-trail-taco-bell-takes-on-big-chicken-through-family-debates/</link>
					<comments>/campaign-trail-taco-bell-takes-on-big-chicken-through-family-debates/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/campaign-trail-taco-bell-takes-on-big-chicken-through-family-debates/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Campaign Trail is our analysis of some of the best new creative efforts from the marketing world. View past columns in the archives here. Forget chicken sandwich wars and chicken tender battles: Taco Bell wants diners to think differently about “Big Chicken” altogether. The QSR in March launched its Cantina Chicken menu nationwide, leaning on [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<div class="editor-note">
<p><em>Campaign Trail is our analysis of some of the best new creative efforts from the marketing world. View past columns in the archives here.</em></p>
</div>
<p>Forget chicken sandwich wars and chicken tender battles: Taco Bell wants diners to think differently about “Big Chicken” altogether. The QSR in March launched its Cantina Chicken menu nationwide, leaning on premium ingredients as it looks to elevate the protein staple.</p>
<p>To further those efforts and plant its flag in the chicken category, the chain launched “Bridging the Chicken Divide,” a campaign that takes a humorous look at family debates around the dining room table and pits Cantina menu fans against “trachickenalists” — the “chicken traditionalists” that ads say are found in every family.</p>
</p>
<p>In a 30-second spot, younger family members dig into Taco Bell’s new chicken offerings while older family members eat familiar, fast-food chicken sandwiches. Heated debate over condiment usage reaches a fever pitch before common ground proves to be “one bite away.”</p>
<p>“I can feel again,” says the dad, before uttering a guttural chirp. The campaign premiered on Sept. 26 and is running across broadcast, connected TV and social media.</p>
<p>“We need to make sure that people think of us as a chicken destination, because when you think of chicken, you think of KFC, Chick-fil-A, Popeyes. You don’t think of Taco Bell,” said Caroline Johnson, associate creative director at the chain’s longtime creative agency, Deutsch. “The brief was disrupting chicken.”</p>
<h3>Generational divide</h3>
<p>To promote the Cantina Chicken menu, Taco Bell and Deutsch wanted to do more than produce product-focused spots. The family table construct allowed the brand to make the “argument” in a more persuasive, relatable way.</p>
<p>“The family divide is just something that everyone has,” Johnson said. “Everyone has that person in their family who’s like, ‘Let me tell you how things were and how they should always be.’”</p>
<p>In “Bridging the Chicken Divide,” these arguments take place as debates over mayo versus avocado verde salsa or the inclusion of pickles. The humor gets a touch of innuendo when one older person says, “Please tell me you’re using a condiment.” But the agency team was wary of random humor for its own sake.</p>
<p>“This always happens with a comedy spot: You shoot so much stuff, and whatever’s making you laugh on set is usually what ends up in the spot,” Johnson said. “We tried the condom joke, we tried some other stuff that was maybe too far, but you go too far to see where the line is.”</p>
</p>
<p>That humor reoccurs in a 30-second spot, “Holiday, Divided,” released on Oct. 31. The new ad gives the family table argument a festive spin, with one parent chastising, “A burrito on what could be Gam Gam’s last holiday?” Finding the right comedic edge allows Taco Bell to speak authentically with its target consumers in the Gen Z cohort. </p>
<p>“They’re all about the being themselves and having open and authentic conversations, and I think Taco Bell uses that same perspective within how we like to phrase our messaging,” said Derek Smith, creative director at Deutsch.</p>
<p>A focus on Gen Z also influenced the casting of Xolo Maridueña (“Cobra Kai,” “Blue Beetle”) as the external commentator in the spot. Taco Bell in recent years has teamed with younger brand ambassadors like actor-comedian Pete Davidson and singer-songwriter Omar Apollo to make its case directly to younger consumers. </p>
<p>“We’re a legacy, establishment brand. There’s a certain level of authenticity that I think we can hit and that we cannot hit,” Johnson explained. “Bringing in someone who was a little more up-and-coming, who felt a little fresher and more authentic to the demographic as the voice of reason, rather than this big corporation talking to you, helped smooth the message.”</p>
</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/campaign-trail-taco-bell-takes-on-big-chicken-through-family-debates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to pick the right Google Business Profile categories</title>
		<link>/how-to-pick-the-right-google-business-profile-categories/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-pick-the-right-google-business-profile-categories/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-pick-the-right-google-business-profile-categories/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Categories on your Google Business Profile (GBP) are among the top factors for local search rankings. It’s essential to choose the right primary and secondary categories to ensure your business appears in relevant searches.  If you’re unsure how to select the best categories for your GBP, this article will guide you through the process. How [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>Categories on your Google Business Profile (GBP) are among the top factors for local search rankings. </p>
<p>It’s essential to choose the right primary and secondary categories to ensure your business appears in relevant searches. </p>
<p>If you’re unsure how to select the best categories for your GBP, this article will guide you through the process.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-choose-the-best-primary-category-for-gbp">How to choose the best primary category for GBP</h2>
<p>Choosing the right primary category for your business isn’t always straightforward. </p>
<p>The many relevant options in industries like dentistry or HVAC can make selecting the best fit challenging.</p>
<p>Since the primary category has the most impact on ranking your Google Business Profile for relevant searches, it’s essential to identify the optimal choice.</p>
<p>This process becomes much easier if you have access to Places Scout – a local rank-tracking tool with a GBP category selection feature. </p>
<p>Run a report for your top keywords, go to the <em>Leads</em> section, create a LeadGen Report, and click on <em>Category Analysis</em> to view the primary categories competitors are using successfully.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="788" height="831" alt="Places Scout" class="wp-image-447901" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout.png.webp 788w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-321x338.png.webp 321w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-569x600.png.webp 569w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-107x113.png.webp 107w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-768x810.png.webp 768w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 788px) 100vw, 788px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout.png.webp"/><noscript><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="788" height="831" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout.png.webp" alt="Places Scout" class="wp-image-447901" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout.png.webp 788w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-321x338.png.webp 321w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-569x600.png.webp 569w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-107x113.png.webp 107w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Places-Scout-768x810.png.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 788px) 100vw, 788px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>Now, you can see a list of all the categories the competitors ranking for your top keywords are using on their listings.</p>
<p>Alternatively, you can download a free extension from PlePer. When you click on a GBP listing, the extension will pop up a ton of info about the listing, including all the categories they use.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="363" height="614" alt="PlePer - Chrome extension showing GBP categories" class="wp-image-447902" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories.png.webp 363w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-200x338.png.webp 200w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-355x600.png.webp 355w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-67x113.png.webp 67w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 363px) 100vw, 363px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories.png.webp"/><noscript><img decoding="async" width="363" height="614" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories.png.webp" alt="PlePer - Chrome extension showing GBP categories" class="wp-image-447902" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories.png.webp 363w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-200x338.png.webp 200w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-355x600.png.webp 355w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/PlePer-Chrome-extension-showing-GBP-categories-67x113.png.webp 67w" sizes="(max-width: 363px) 100vw, 363px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>The first category on the list is the primary category. Look at all the top competing listings in your area and note the primary categories they are using.</p>
<p>Once you know the primary categories the competition uses most often, you can decide which primary category is best for your listing.</p>
<p>Test different primary categories to see which provides the best ranking boosts for your top keywords. Just don’t change the categories too often.</p>
<p>Wait a few weeks after a category change to assess rankings and change the category again if necessary.</p>
<p><strong><em>Dig deeper: </em></strong><strong><em>6 Google Business Profile questions asked and answered</em></strong></p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gbp-secondary-category-optimization">GBP secondary category optimization</h2>
<p>Although the primary category may be the most important in terms of the ranking value it provides, your listing can have nine secondary category spots. </p>
<p>I typically recommend filling all nine secondary slots with relevant categories whenever possible. </p>
<p>You can use the same tools I mentioned above to find the most relevant secondary categories. You can also try Jepto’s Google Business Profile Discovery tool to help you find more relevant categories.</p>
<p>Google constantly changes, removes and adds new categories to GBP. Make sure to check monthly or quarterly for additional relevant categories you may want to add to your listing. </p>
<p>Also, keep in mind that categories can have different names depending on where in the world you are located.</p>
<p>For example, in Australia they have a category for “tradesmen” that is not offered in the U.S. or Canada.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="316" height="262" alt="GBP category - Tradesmen" class="wp-image-447903" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen.png.webp 316w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen-136x113.png.webp 136w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 316px) 100vw, 316px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen.png.webp"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="316" height="262" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen.png.webp" alt="GBP category - Tradesmen" class="wp-image-447903" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen.png.webp 316w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-category-Tradesmen-136x113.png.webp 136w" sizes="(max-width: 316px) 100vw, 316px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>If you are working with a global business, it’s important to ensure you add the most relevant categories based on the region.</p>
<p><!-- START INLINE FORM --></p>
<div class="nl-inline-form border py-2 px-1 my-2">
<div class="row align-items-center nl-inline-container">
<div class="col-12 col-lg-3 col-xl-4 pe-md-0 pb-2 pb-lg-0">
<p class="inline-form-text text-center mb-0">Get the newsletter search marketers rely on.</p>
</p></div>
</p></div>
</div>
<p><!-- END INLINE FORM --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-cyan-bluish-gray-color has-css-opacity has-cyan-bluish-gray-background-color has-background"/>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-predefined-services">Predefined services</h2>
<p>Another major benefit to adding secondary categories is that under each category, there is an option to select pre-defined services. </p>
<p>Pre-defined services can help boost rankings a bit, so as you are adding secondary categories, make sure to click on each one and check off all relevant services.</p>
<p>The categories “Contractor” and “Handyman/Handywoman/Handyperson” are extremely similar, but they have some unique services under each.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="688" height="718" alt="GBP - Contractor category" class="wp-image-447904" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category.png.webp 688w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-324x338.png.webp 324w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-575x600.png.webp 575w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-108x113.png.webp 108w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 688px) 100vw, 688px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category.png.webp"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="688" height="718" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category.png.webp" alt="GBP - Contractor category" class="wp-image-447904" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category.png.webp 688w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-324x338.png.webp 324w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-575x600.png.webp 575w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Contractor-category-108x113.png.webp 108w" sizes="(max-width: 688px) 100vw, 688px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="679" height="486" alt="GBP - Handyperson category" class="wp-image-447905" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category.png.webp 679w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category-472x338.png.webp 472w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category-158x113.png.webp 158w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 679px) 100vw, 679px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category.png.webp"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="679" height="486" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category.png.webp" alt="GBP - Handyperson category" class="wp-image-447905" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category.png.webp 679w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category-472x338.png.webp 472w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/GBP-Handyperson-category-158x113.png.webp 158w" sizes="(max-width: 679px) 100vw, 679px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>Jepto’s Google Business Profile Discovery tool can also help here, as it will tell you all the services associated with each category.</p>
<p><strong><em>Dig deeper: </em></strong><strong><em>5 top tips to boost your local SEO efforts</em></strong></p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-can-you-switch-the-primary-category-depending-on-the-season-nbsp">Can you switch the primary category depending on the season? </h2>
<p>Absolutely! This is a vital strategy for seasonal businesses like HVAC, lawn care, farms and more. </p>
<p>Adjusting the primary category to match seasonal demand allows these businesses to optimize their visibility for relevant searches year-round.</p>
<p>If you’re in the HVAC industry, make sure to switch your GBP category from “air conditioning repair service” to “furnace repair service” at least a few weeks before the cold weather hits. </p>
<p>This ensures Google has time to reassess your business profile and rank it for furnace and heating terms.</p>
<p>Many other industries also benefit from this strategy. For example, a lawn care business that does snow removal in the winter will want to switch its primary category from “lawn care” to “snow removal service” a few weeks before the first snowfall hits. </p>
<p>Suppose your business operates a haunted house during the fall. In that case, there’s a specific category for that, which can boost your profile’s relevance and give you a competitive edge in “haunted house near me” searches. </p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="688" height="257" alt="Haunted house near me" class="wp-image-447906" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me.png.webp 688w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me-600x224.png.webp 600w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me-200x75.png.webp 200w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 688px) 100vw, 688px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me.png.webp"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="688" height="257" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me.png.webp" alt="Haunted house near me" class="wp-image-447906" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me.png.webp 688w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me-600x224.png.webp 600w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Haunted-house-near-me-200x75.png.webp 200w" sizes="(max-width: 688px) 100vw, 688px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>Once the Halloween season ends, you can easily switch to a more relevant category for the winter months to maintain visibility for your core services.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-avoid-the-local-filter-with-strategic-category-tactics">Avoid the local filter with strategic category tactics</h2>
<p>If you have multiple listings verified at the same address, such as a practitioner or department listing, it’s crucial to carefully select categories for each.</p>
<p>Overlapping categories can trigger Google’s local filter, reducing your visibility. To avoid this, ensure that each listing at the same address has distinct categories.</p>
<p>For example, a dental clinic with both a main office listing and a practitioner listing should assign unique categories to each.</p>
<p>The main office might use “dentist,” while the practitioner listing could use “emergency dentist” or “pediatric dentist.”</p>
<p>You need to confirm using local rank tracking grids that the listings are not actually filtering each other. Even if they have separate categories, this filtering can still happen if the categories are too similar.</p>
<p>If you see an irregular pattern with inverted pins (like the one below), the local filter is likely at work.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1488" height="893" alt="Google's local filter at work" class="wp-image-447907" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work.png.webp 1488w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-563x338.png.webp 563w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-800x480.png.webp 800w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-188x113.png.webp 188w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-768x461.png.webp 768w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work.png.webp"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1488" height="893" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work.png.webp" alt="Google's local filter at work" class="wp-image-447907" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work.png.webp 1488w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-563x338.png.webp 563w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-800x480.png.webp 800w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-188x113.png.webp 188w,https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/Googles-local-filter-at-work-768x461.png.webp 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1488px) 100vw, 1488px"/></noscript></figure>
</div>
<p>You can also use category optimization to get your listing unfiltered if you are being filtered by nearby business listings you don’t have control over. </p>
<p>For example, realtors tend to have major issues with the local filter when many individual realtor listings are verified to the same broker’s address. </p>
<p>If you’re in a position like this, try changing your primary category to something none of the other listings use.</p>
<p><strong><em>Dig deeper: </em></strong><strong><em>11 local SEO tools you should be using</em></strong></p>
</div>
<p><em>Contributing authors are invited to create content for Search Engine Land and are chosen for their expertise and contribution to the search community. Our contributors work under the oversight of the editorial staff and contributions are checked for quality and relevance to our readers. The opinions they express are their own.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-pick-the-right-google-business-profile-categories/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Brands Can Get Diwali Right</title>
		<link>/how-brands-can-get-diwali-right/</link>
					<comments>/how-brands-can-get-diwali-right/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-brands-can-get-diwali-right/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As 1 billion people worldwide get ready to celebrate Diwali, known as the festival of lights, brands are also looking to enter this cultural moment and capitalize on this holiday. Target is selling a wide range of Diwali items, including books, food, decorations and games. Costco is selling a 10-piece Diwali Diya set. Hallmark has [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>As 1 billion people worldwide get ready to celebrate Diwali, known as the festival of lights, brands are also looking to enter this cultural moment and capitalize on this holiday.</p>
<p>Target is selling a wide range of Diwali items, including books, food, decorations and games. Costco is selling a 10-piece <a href="https://www.costco.com/diwali-diya-10-piece-set.product.4000262641.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Diwali Diya set</a>. Hallmark has a range of Diwali <a href="https://www.hallmark.com/diwali/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">greeting cards</a>. Anastasia Beverly Hills had a Diwali collaboration <a href="https://www.instagram.com/anastasiabeverlyhills/reel/DBeoBw4htST/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">makeup set</a> in partnership with influencer Aditya Madiraju that sold out in less than 14 hours online. And Cartier hosted their first-ever <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sofiaeatsnyc/video/7429411363837103406" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Diwali party</a> at their mansion on Fifth Avenue in New York City this year.</p>
<p>As the child of Indian immigrants who grew up in the U.S., I was bullied for being different: for eating different foods, for listening to different music, and for celebrating different holidays. It’s heartening to see my children growing up in an environment where holidays like Diwali are being embraced by so many. As marketers, it’s our responsibility to enter these cultural moments authentically and respectfully. Here are three things to keep in mind if we want to get Diwali right.</p>
<div class="row justify-content-center">
<div class="col-12">
<section class="section section--teaser section--teaser_partners section--teaser_partners--horizontal px-0 py-4">
<div class="section--teaser_partner"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adweek.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/starbucks-aapi-summer-berry-2024.jpg?w=640&amp;h=360&amp;crop=1" alt="Boba-inspired beverages Starbucks Refreshers fail to credit the rich history of the Asian beverage." class="image image--partner"/>                     </div>
</section>
</div></div>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading">Understand what Diwali means</h4>
<p>For my children, who are third-generation Indian American, some of their fondest memories with their grandparents, aunt, uncle, and cousins have been centered around Diwali.</p>
<p>Dressing up in Indian outfits that were brought from India. Helping with stringing up lights, flowers, and other decorations. Lining up diya lamps, sitting and sometimes squirming while their grandparents say prayers, and waiting for the moment they can devour Indian rotis and sweets and slurp down mango lassi. Lighting sparklers together and setting off fireworks on the long driveway as the family heads in to exchange gifts and play a competitive game of Crazy Sevens that goes into the late hours of the evening.</p>
<p>Diwali (also known as Deepavali, meaning a row of lights) is one of the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/10/23/business/diwali-products-marketing-us-mainstream-cec/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">most important festivals</a> in the Hindu religion. It also holds meaning for Jains, Sikhs, and Buddhists and is celebrated not just in India but all over the world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-brands-can-get-diwali-right/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google updates crawl budget docs for large sites with differing mobile and desktop pages and links</title>
		<link>/google-updates-crawl-budget-docs-for-large-sites-with-differing-mobile-and-desktop-pages-and-links/</link>
					<comments>/google-updates-crawl-budget-docs-for-large-sites-with-differing-mobile-and-desktop-pages-and-links/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/google-updates-crawl-budget-docs-for-large-sites-with-differing-mobile-and-desktop-pages-and-links/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google added a new best practice in its crawl budget documentation to say it is best practice to ensure all links are present on the mobile version, as it is on your desktop version, if your page. If you do not do this, the discovery of new pages can be slower if the mobile version [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>Google added a new best practice in its crawl budget documentation to say it is best practice to ensure all links are present on the mobile version, as it is on your desktop version, if your page.  If you do not do this, the discovery of new pages can be slower if the mobile version does not include all the links that are currently available on the desktop version.</p>
<p><strong>What changed. </strong>Google added a new bullet point to <a href="https://developers.google.com/search/docs/crawling-indexing/large-site-managing-crawl-budget#updates">this section of the crawl budget documentation</a> page: </p>
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>“If your site uses separate HTML for mobile and desktop versions, provide the same set of links on the mobile version as you have on the desktop version. If it’s not possible to provide the same set of links on the mobile version, ensure that they’re included in a <a href="https://developers.google.com/search/docs/crawling-indexing/sitemaps/overview">sitemap</a> file. Google only <a href="https://developers.google.com/search/docs/crawling-indexing/mobile/mobile-sites-mobile-first-indexing">indexes the mobile version</a> of pages, and limiting the links shown there can slow down discovery of new pages.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Why Google add this</strong>. Google wrote this to explain that if you do not do this, it can slow the crawl of your mobile pages. Google wrote:</p>
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow">
<p>“For large websites with separate HTML on mobile and desktop versions, the discovery of new pages can be slower if the mobile version does not include all the links that are present on the desktop version.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Why we care. </strong>If you large site uses both a mobile and desktop version of the site and the links on some of those pages do not match, it can cause discovery issues for your new content.  If you want to ensure everything is optimal and the speed of crawl is fine, make sure to have the content on those pages to be the same, including the links.  You can always go with a responsive design to simply this in the future.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/google-updates-crawl-budget-docs-for-large-sites-with-differing-mobile-and-desktop-pages-and-links/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Rao’s picked Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade for a marketing breakthrough</title>
		<link>/why-raos-picked-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-for-a-marketing-breakthrough/</link>
					<comments>/why-raos-picked-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-for-a-marketing-breakthrough/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-raos-picked-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-for-a-marketing-breakthrough/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Since the 1970s, Rao’s has been one of New York City’s most exclusive restaurants, patronized by the famous and infamous alike. In the early ‘90s, the Harlem institution turned its marinara sauce into a regional retail brand. And in the last few years, Rao’s Homemade has been taken on a “rocketship,” explained Alan Creveling, vice [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>Since the 1970s, Rao’s has been one of New York City’s <a href="https://www.vanityfair.com/culture/2016/10/raos-new-york-exclusive-restaurant">most exclusive restaurants</a>, patronized by the famous and infamous alike. In the early ‘90s, the Harlem institution turned its marinara sauce into a regional retail brand. And in the last few years, Rao’s Homemade has been taken on a “rocketship,” explained Alan Creveling, vice president of marketing at Campbell’s Distinctive Brands, which oversees the brand.</p>
<p>“Over the last six to eight years, [Rao’s has] really grown leaps and bounds. It&#8217;s going to be a billion dollars in sales. We&#8217;re number one in market share in the category, and we&#8217;re doing it with a younger audience,” the executive said.</p>
<p>Along with its sales success, Rao’s has seen its sauce become a part of the pop culture zeitgeist on social media and its profile rise after the $2.7 billion acquisition of parent company Sovos Brands by the Campbell Soup Company in March 2024. </p>
<p>Still, only about 65% of consumers are aware of the brand, giving it room to grow through marketing. Rao’s awareness-focused media spend puts the brand on national TV during NFL and college football broadcasts. As brands increasingly turn to live sports, especially football, to make an impact, Rao’s is looking to breakthrough creatively with a new campaign that debuts on Nov. 2 during a highly anticipated matchup between Penn State and Ohio State. The effort was created with agency BSSP.</p>
<p><iframe allow="autoplay; fullscreen; picture-in-picture; clipboard-write" frameborder="0" src="https://player.vimeo.com/video/1025114958?badge=0&amp;autopause=0&amp;player_id=0&amp;app_id=58479" style="position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;" title="RAO'S_Soil_15_16x9"></iframe></p>
<p>“The look and feel are going to be completely different than things we&#8217;ve done in the past, but it&#8217;s true to who we are as a brand, true to our delicious ingredients and true to our Italian roots, and that&#8217;s going to be the real differentiator with this advertising,” Creveling said.</p>
<p>Three 15-second spots viewed by Marketing Dive focus on the ingredients, heritage and craftsmanship that set Rao’s apart from the pack. The campaign will run on broadcast, connected TV, online video, social media and digital out-of-home channels.</p>
<h3 class="standard-heading">Floating on the airwaves</h3>
<p>While football <a href="https://www.sportico.com/business/media/2024/nfl-posts-93-of-top-100-tv-broadcasts-2023-1234761753/">dominates broadcast TV viewership</a>, a few non-pigskin events still have the cultural cachet to breakthrough, like the State of the Union address, the Academy Awards and Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade. With that in mind, Rao’s will make its parade debut later this month with its own float, an experience Creveling described as “humbling, but also really exciting.” </p>
<p>“I&#8217;ve never designed a float. I have no idea how to do that,” the executive said. “The first thought people have is, ‘Oh, you should just put your jar on a float.’ Okay, I would like that. But [Macy’s] needs to tell a story in less than 90 seconds about what&#8217;s going on here.”</p>
<p>After almost a year-long process from concept to execution, Rao’s and Macy’s on Thanksgiving will introduce the Pasta Knight, punning off a tradition shared by 86% of all U.S. households, Creveling said. The Knight is covered in bronze, die-cut pasta “armor” and bears a cheese grater shield as he battles a dragon, with a surprise element that Creveling said, to borrow Gen Z and millennial slang, “is going to be fire.”</p>
<p>“It&#8217;s just taking an idea that everyone knows and just making a creative piece that can bring people&#8217;s imaginations out in a real bright environment,” the executive said.</p>
<h3 class="standard-heading">Joining the family</h3>
<p>Fans of Rao’s sauces have nothing to worry about with the brand’s acquisition by Campbell Soup: The company is not changing the sauce recipe. But the deal is expected to help the brand accelerate its growth on the path it has charted for years.</p>
<p>“There is a recognition from the Campbell side that we want to make sure this thing is running like it&#8217;s been running — we don&#8217;t want to get too involved, unless we need to,” Creveling said of the deal. “There&#8217;s been an autonomy throughout this entire process that has led to really good work, and as we talk, we get best practices and we can make it even better.”</p>
<p>That will likely impact Rao’s marketing, a function that the executive has overseen since before Campbell Soup acquired Sovos.</p>
<section class="storylines-carousel-wrapper hide-small show-large" id="desktop-carousel"/>
<p>“We&#8217;re very proud of the work we&#8217;ve done… but Campbell&#8217;s gives us access to so many more resources when it comes to the insights game — to numbers, to how we can reach new audiences — and really can take us to the level that we need to go,” Creveling said.</p>
</p></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/why-raos-picked-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-for-a-marketing-breakthrough/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Very and TK Maxx reprise last year&#039;s Christmas ads for 2024</title>
		<link>/very-and-tk-maxx-reprise-last-years-christmas-ads-for-2024/</link>
					<comments>/very-and-tk-maxx-reprise-last-years-christmas-ads-for-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/very-and-tk-maxx-reprise-last-years-christmas-ads-for-2024/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The campaigns were created by The Gate and Wieden &#38; Kennedy London respectively.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><img decoding="async" src="https://cached.imagescaler.hbpl.co.uk/resize/scaleHeight/815/cached.offlinehbpl.hbpl.co.uk/news/OMC/MixCollage-01-Nov-2024-11-42-AM-7133.jpg" style="width: 100%" /></p>
<div>The campaigns were created by The Gate and Wieden &amp; Kennedy London respectively.</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/very-and-tk-maxx-reprise-last-years-christmas-ads-for-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gap&#8217;s Creator Choir Throws It Back to the &#8217;90s In Holiday Ad</title>
		<link>/gaps-creator-choir-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-in-holiday-ad/</link>
					<comments>/gaps-creator-choir-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-in-holiday-ad/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gaps-creator-choir-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-in-holiday-ad/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Gap has been harking back to the ads of its 1990s and 2000s heydays throughout this year as it aims to recapture its cool, and its holiday spot is no exception. “Give Your Gift” assembles a cozy choir of musical creators and rising stars clad in Gap’s CashSoft “cashmere-like” sweaters, scarves, and knits. Together they [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div>
<p>Gap has been harking back to the ads of its 1990s and 2000s heydays throughout this year as it aims to recapture its cool, and its holiday spot is no exception.</p>
<p>“Give Your Gift” assembles a cozy choir of musical creators and rising stars clad in Gap’s CashSoft “cashmere-like” sweaters, scarves, and knits. Together they deliver an a capella cover of Janet Jackson’s 1997 bop “Together Again.”</p>
<p>The joyful work, directed by Samuel Bradley, is the first campaign under the leadership of CMO Fabiola Torres, who joined the brand from Pepsi in May. </p>
<p>In a statement, Torres said Gap wanted to be where its customers were, delivering engaging, style-led content. </p>
<p>“Partnering with the right talent drives cultural connections and builds community with new audiences. This year’s campaign champions creators’ authentic voices and styles, celebrating their creativity and originality,” she said.</p>
<p>Creators featured in the chorus include Nyjah Music and Zyah Rhythm, a brother duo known for their song covers that have appeared on millions of Instagram feeds around the world. </p>
<p>Paige Fish, an 18-year-old TikToker, and soul singer Lamont Landers also feature alongside Liamani, a 16-year-old singer and actress.</p>
<p>The work will launch in stores and across digital media, video, social, and Gap brand channels. </p>
<p>It comes as the retailer’s investment in nostalgia-driven marketing designed to capture millennial and Gen Z audiences is paying off, turning around years of sluggish sales.</p>
<h4 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>‘Nowstalgia’ is helping Gap win over Gen Z </strong></h4>
<p>Re-entering the cultural conversation has been at the forefront of Gap’s reboot, kickstarted in 2023 by former Mattel exec Richard Dickson when he took over the CEO role at parent company Gap Inc.</p>
<p>Recent work from the eponymous retailer, including “Linen Moves” and a back-to-school campaign called “Just Dance,” have harked back to an aesthetic reminiscent of ’90s and ’00s Gap ads showing troupes of dancers wearing khakis and denim. </p>
<p>The retailer isn’t just leaning on nostalgia though. It’s been tapping relevant artists, including Gen Z favorites Troye Sivan and Tyla, to freshen things up.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/gaps-creator-choir-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-in-holiday-ad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google fixes supplemental feed limitation in Merchant Center Next</title>
		<link>/google-fixes-supplemental-feed-limitation-in-merchant-center-next/</link>
					<comments>/google-fixes-supplemental-feed-limitation-in-merchant-center-next/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[shyuni]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/google-fixes-supplemental-feed-limitation-in-merchant-center-next/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center Next resolved a previous limitation that prevented users from working with pre-prepared supplemental feeds in Google Sheets. Merchants can now use existing Google Sheets for supplemental feeds, eliminating the previous requirement to create sheets from scratch or use alternative methods. Why we care. This will save time for ecommerce managers and merchants [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div itemprop="articleBody">
<div class="bialty-container">
<p>Google Merchant Center Next resolved a previous limitation that prevented users from working with pre-prepared supplemental feeds in Google Sheets.</p>
<p>Merchants can now use existing Google Sheets for supplemental feeds, eliminating the previous requirement to create sheets from scratch or use alternative methods.</p>
<p><strong>Why we care.</strong> This will save time for ecommerce managers and merchants and allow continued use of existing spreadsheet templates. Plus, it simplifies the feed management process in Google Merchant Center.</p>
<p><strong>Big picture.</strong> Previously reported by industry observer Emmanuel Flossie on LinkedIn, the issue restricted merchants from leveraging pre-existing spreadsheets for their product feeds. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/feedarmy_finally-google-merchant-center-now-allows-activity-7256993194846892033-uNkV/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop" target="_blank" rel="noopener">The recent update</a> removes this technical constraint.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="800" height="450" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds-800x450.webp" alt="Streamline Product Feeds" class="wp-image-447946" srcset="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds-800x450.webp 800w, https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds-600x338.webp 600w, https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds-200x113.webp 200w, https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds-768x432.webp 768w, https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/seloads/2024/11/streamline-product-feeds.webp 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"/></figure>
<p>This isn’t the first time advertisers have had issues with Merchant Center Next and supplemental feeds. In July it wasn’t clear whether advertisers could use the supplemental feed and the solution for that was tedious. This solution makes the compatibility more straightforward.</p>
<p><strong>What’s next.</strong> Merchants using Google Merchant Center Next should review their current supplemental feed setup to take advantage of the new functionality.</p>
</div>
<hr/>
<div class="google-news-link text-center">
							<a class="" href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqBggKMLXKIzD8vAQ?hl=en-US&amp;gl=US&amp;ceid=US%3Aen" target="_blank" aria-label="opens in a new tab" rel="noopener"><em>Add Search Engine Land to your Google News feed.</em>    <img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="img-fluid" alt="Google News" width="140" height="38" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/themes/tdm-editorial/img/icons/google_news.png"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="img-fluid" src="https://searchengineland.com/wp-content/themes/tdm-editorial/img/icons/google_news.png" alt="Google News" width="140" height="38"/></noscript></a></p>
<hr/></div>
<div class="row">
<div class="col-12 col-md-6">
<div class="container-fluid px-0 sel-new-articles">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-12">
<p class="pb-1">New on Search Engine Land</p>
<section class="global-content-stream">
</section></div>
</p></div>
</div></div>
</p></div>
<p><!-- START EOS SPACE --></p>
<p><!-- END EOS SPACE -->					</p>
<div class="about-author">
<p>About the author</p>
<div class="information">
<div class="author-module">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-12 col-lg-3 text-center">
<div class="avatar">
						<img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="img-fluid rounded-circle avatar-border" alt="Anu Adegbola" width="140" height="140" src="https://searchengineland.com/anu-adegbola-2"/><noscript><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="img-fluid rounded-circle avatar-border" src="https://searchengineland.com/anu-adegbola-2" alt="Anu Adegbola" width="140" height="140"/></noscript>
											</div>
</p></div>
<div class="col-12 col-lg-9">
<div class="about">
<p>						<span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', 'Noto Sans', 'Liberation Sans', Arial, sans-serif, 'Apple Color Emoji', 'Segoe UI Emoji', 'Segoe UI Symbol', 'Noto Color Emoji'; font-size: 16px;">Anu Adegbola has been Paid Media Editor of Search Engine Land</span><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', 'Noto Sans', 'Liberation Sans', Arial, sans-serif, 'Apple Color Emoji', 'Segoe UI Emoji', 'Segoe UI Symbol', 'Noto Color Emoji'; font-size: 16px;"> since 2024. She covers</span><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, 'Segoe UI', Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', 'Noto Sans', 'Liberation Sans', Arial, sans-serif, 'Apple Color Emoji', 'Segoe UI Emoji', 'Segoe UI Symbol', 'Noto Color Emoji'; font-size: 16px;"> paid search, paid social, retail media, video and more.</p>
<p>In 2008, Anu&#8217;s career started with</p>
<p></span><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;"> delivering digital marketing campaigns (mostly but not exclusively Paid Search) by building strategies, maximising ROI, automating repetitive processes and bringing efficiency from every part of marketing departments through inspiring leadership both on agency, client and marketing tech side.</span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;"> </span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;">Outside editing Search Engine Land article she is the founder of PPC networking event &#8211; PPC Live and host of </span></span><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;">weekly podcast PPCChat Roundup.</span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;"> </span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #212529; font-family: system-ui, -apple-system, Segoe UI, Roboto, Helvetica Neue, Noto Sans, Liberation Sans, Arial, sans-serif, Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Noto Color Emoji;"><span style="font-size: 16px;">She is also an international speaker with some of the stages she has presented on being SMX (US), SMX (Munich), Friends of Search (Amsterdam), brightonSEO, The Marketing Meetup, HeroConf (PPC Hero), SearchLove, BiddableWorld, SESLondon, PPC Chat Live, AdWorld Experience (Bologna) and more.</span></span></p>
</p></div>
</p></div>
</p></div>
</p></div>
</p></div>
</div>
<p>
					</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/google-fixes-supplemental-feed-limitation-in-merchant-center-next/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!-- plugin=object-cache-pro client=phpredis metric#hits=940 metric#misses=55 metric#hit-ratio=94.5 metric#bytes=303302 metric#prefetches=0 metric#store-reads=73 metric#store-writes=3 metric#store-hits=78 metric#store-misses=52 metric#sql-queries=4 metric#ms-total=110.59 metric#ms-cache=15.30 metric#ms-cache-avg=0.2039 metric#ms-cache-ratio=13.8 -->
